Contact

8985370840 (Mobile) akshay951228@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ akshay951228 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Deep Learning
Computer Vision
Tensorflow

Certifications

Visual Studio Code for Python Developers

Akshay kumar Arasavalli

Ex-Data scientist | Computer Vision | Deep Learning Hyderabad

Summary

Just another Self Motivated, Always Curious and Always Learning Guy who loves to Invent and Innovate stuff. Favorite quote: "Whatever it takes"

I have an extensive Research and Development experience in Deep Learning, Machine Learning,

Computer Vision/Image Processing Projects.

Converting R&D work to production level work. Love to experiment

Present working Tech Stack: PyTorch, TensorFlow, Python,Flask,TensorRT, REST APIs

Feel free to ping me, to know more!

Experience

jotter ai Data Scientist August 2018 - June 2020 (1 year 11 months) Hyderabad Area, India

StartUp Gurukul Developer Intern May 2017 - March 2018 (11 months) Visakhapatnam

Education

RAJIV GANDHI UNIVERSITY OF KNOWLEDGE TECHNOLOGIES, NUZVID

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2014 - 2018)